let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the full form of SEBI?",
        answer: "C. Securities and Exchange Board of India",
        options: [
            "A. Stocks and Emission Bank of India",
            "B. Stocks and Exchange Board of India",
            "C. Securities and Exchange Board of India",
            "D. Securities and Exchange Bank of India"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the Largest Bank in India?",
        answer: "B. SBI",
        options: [
            "A. ICICI",
            "B. SBI",
            "C. HDFC",
            "D. Punjab National Bank"
        ]
    },{
        numb: 3,
        question: "In 2013, the price of 1 litre milk was Rs 44 and now the price of 1 litre milk is Rs 60. What is this term called?",
        answer: "D. Inflation",
        options: [
            "A. Intensification",
            "B. Expansion of money",
            "C. Deflation",
            "D. Inflation"
        ]
    },{
        numb: 4,
        question: "A pool of money managed by a professional Fund Manager is called?",
        answer: "A. Mutual Funds",
        options: [
            "A. Mutual Funds",
            "B. Bank",
            "C. Forex",
            "D. Stock Market"
        ]
    },{
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the full form of ATM?",
        answer: "A. Automated Teller Machine",
        options: [
            "A. Automated Teller Machine",
            "B. Automatic Teller Machine",
            "C. All Time Money",
            "D. Automatic Transaction Machine"
        ]
    },{
        numb: 6,
        question: "The exchange of goods and services between two or more parties without the use of money is called?",
        answer: "C. Barter System",
        options: [
            "A. Currency-less System",
            "B. Exchange System",
            "C. Barter System",
            "D. Profit System"
        ]
    },{
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the strongest currency in the World?",
        answer: "B. Kuwaiti Dinar",
        options: [
            "A. US Dollar",
            "B. Kuwaiti Dinar",
            "C. British Pound",
            "D. Euro"
        ]
    },{
        numb: 8,
        question: "PAN refers to:",
        answer: "B. Permanent Account Number",
        options: [
            "A. Primary Account Number",
            "B. Permanent Account Number",
            "C. Public Account Number",
            "D. Personal Account Number"
        ]
    },{
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which of the following may lead to a financial problem?",
        answer: "A. Overspending",
        options: [
            "A. Overspending",
            "B. Categorizing your expenses",
            "C. Understanding your spending",
            "D. Budgeting"
        ]
    },{
        numb: 10,
        question: "KYC means:",
        answer: "C. Know Your Customer",
        options: [
            "A. Know Your Company",
            "B. Know Your Credit",
            "C. Know Your Customer",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
];